smallcase.com 2019-05-21

# smallcase | Privacy

Privacy matters. Privacy is what allows us to determine who we are and what we do - Edward Snowden

smallcase.com is a product by smallcase Technologies Private Limited (hereinafter referred to as smallcase Technologies ). smallcase Technologies is committed to safeguarding any information submitted to us on our website and or services. The privacy notice provides you with a summary of the type of information collected by us, policy regarding use of that information and measures taken to safeguard that information.

## User Consent

By submitting Personal Information through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly give your voluntary consent to the collection, use and disclosure of the Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Information you provided to us

  * If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply.
  * When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional information.
  * We may collect Personal Information from you, such as your first and last name, phone, e-mail address, age etc. when you apply for creating/opening an account with one of our partners - brokers, advisors etc.
  * We may also collect Personal Information on the Site or through the Services when we make clear that we are collecting it and you voluntarily provide the same, for example when you submit an application for employment.
  * You must ensure to recheck the information or data being provided to us. In case if any of the data/information is found to be inaccurate or incorrect, the same shall be informed to us for immediate amendment. We shall not be responsible for the authenticity of any information including personal information submitted to us.

## Information collected via technology

  * To make our Site and Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third-party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), and domain name.
  * We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us analyze visitor activity on the Site. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for us.

## Use of personal information

In general, personal Information you submit to us regarding you or your company is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We use such Personal Information in the following ways:

  * To identify you as a user in our system;
  * To provide improved administration of our Site and Services;
  * To provide the Services you request;
  * To improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Site and Services;
  * To send you e-mail notifications
  * To send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes.
  * Protect our services and our users.
  * Market and customer analysis, market research and statistics.
  * To prevent and detect fraud or abuse of our services as well as to prevent, detect and investigate any potential unlawful or prohibited activities.

## Disclosure to third parties

We may be required from time to time to disclose any personal information collected by us to governmental or judicial bodies or agencies or our regulators based on their requirement to comply with the applicable laws including cyber laws.  
We may share your information including personal information to third parties to carry out technical, logistical and other functions on our behalf. (eg. Sending emails or newsletters to users).

## Creation of anonymous information

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as the name and email),We use this Anonymous Information to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation. smallcase Technologies reserves the right to use Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties at its sole discretion.

## Third party websites

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Information or Anonymous Information from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be held responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of information after you click on links to such outside websites.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a browser can record after visiting a web site. We may use cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through our site, or to store user preferences for interacting with the site. If you turn off the option to have cookies stored on your browser, it will affect your experience on smallcase.com

## Security of your information

smallcase Technologies is committed to protecting the security and privacy of your Personal Information. We endeavour to have suitable technical, operational and physical security controls and measures to protect information collected by us that are commensurate with the nature of our business at all times. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.  
Further, despite our efforts to protect your information, if unauthorized persons breach security control measures and illegally use such sensitive/personal data or information, smallcase Technologies, its affiliates and directors shall not be held responsible/liable.

## Retention of information/data

It may be noted that we may retain the data as may be provided to us till such time as may be provided under the law and as required to efficiently provide service to our users

## Amendments/Modifications

This Privacy Policy available on our website is current and valid. However, smallcase Technologies reserves the right to amend/modify any of the sections of this policy at any time and the general public are requested to keep themselves updated for changes by reading the same from time to time

## Contact Information

smallcase welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at

or contact us at the following address:

smallcase Technologies Private Limited  
#51, 3rd Floor, Le Parc Richmonde,  
Richmond Road, Shanthala Nagar,  
Richmond Town, Bangalore - 560025

## Definitions

  * Anonymous Information - Anonymous information means information that does not directly or indirectly identify, and cannot reasonably be used to identify, an individual guest / user
  * Internet Protocol (IP) - Internet Protocol (IP) is the principal set (or communications protocol) of digital message formats and rules for exchanging messages between computers across a single network or a series of interconnected networks, using the Internet Protocol Suite (often referred to as TCP/IP). Messages are exchanged as datagrams, also known as data packets or just packets.
  * Personal Information - Personal Information means any information that relates to a natural person, which, either directly or indirectly, in combination with any other information available, is capable of identifying such person.

### LAST UPDATED ON 1st March 2019
